Evil comes with strings attached.
Pinocchio's Revenge is a horror, mystery film directed by Kevin Tenney.
Defense attorney Jennifer Garrick acquires a Pinocchio
puppet from a condemned serial killer.
Her pre-teen daughter, Zoe, mistakes the puppet as a birthday
present and grows attached to her new friend.
Suddenly, accidents begin to happen to those who cross Zoe.
Zoe claims it's her Pinocchio doll but her therapist thinks otherwise.
Pinocchio promises he'll behave if Zoe will cut his strings...
Jennifer Garrick, played by Rosalind Allen.
David Kaminsky, played by Todd Allen.
Sophia, played by Candace McKenzie.
Zoe Garrick, played by Brit Smith.
Dr. Edwards, played by Aaron Lustig.
Vincent Gotto, played by Lewis van Bergen.
Pinocchio's Revenge is a 1996 American psychological
horror film written and directed by Kevin S.
Tenney and distributed by Trimark Pictures.
It stars Rosalind Allen and Todd Allen and was released direct-to-video.
The film's plot concerns a lawyer who brings home a wooden puppet that was
found buried with a boy supposedly killed by his father.
Her 8-year-old daughter Zoe sees the doll and takes it as her own.
Soon accidents start happening and Jennifer struggles to find the cause as she begins to question her
daughter's wellbeing and whether or not there may be something sinister to the doll.
The movie is closer "to Don Mancini's original intent for Child's Play".
The film was conceptualized as Bad Pinocchio, written as The Pinocchio Syndrome, shot as
Pinocchio, and released as Pinocchio's Revenge on VHS and Laserdisc on 23 September 1997.
The film explores themes of puppet, doll, toy.
The tone is dark and mind_bending.